http://www.photothumb.com/privacy.shtml

Privacy Statement
PhotoThumb.com respects your online time and privacy. Below, we'll describe the privacy practices for this website.
Personal information
At PhotoThumb.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit PhotoThumb.com on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.
There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and email address. We do not collect any personal information without your consent. PhotoThumb.com does not share information about individual users with any third party.
If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.
We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it.
Business relationships
PhotoThumb.com contains links to other websites. PhotoThumb.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Cookies
There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. No cookies are used at this website.
If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, you can contact us at feedback@photothumb.com.
Copyright © 2001-2011 Jarle Aasland. All rights reserved. Privacy statement.
